<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<!--
  ~ BIT Lalpur App
  ~
  ~ Created by Ayaan on 9/11/21, 11:17 PM
  ~ Copyright (c) 2021 . All rights reserved.
  ~ Last modified 9/11/21, 11:14 PM
  -->

<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:layout_height="fill_parent"
    android:background="?attr/colorSurface"
    android:padding="8.0dip"
    android:scrollbars="none">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="@drawable/heading_back"
            android:backgroundTint="?attr/colorPrimary"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:text="Problem Solving and Programming in C Lab"
            android:textColor="@color/textColorSubTitle"
            android:textSize="32.0dip"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"

            android:gravity="center"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:text="List of Programs as Assignments:"
                android:textColor="@color/textColor"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                    android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10.0dip"
                android:gravity="left"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1. Write an interactive program that will read in a +ve integer value and determine the following \n\ni) If the integer is a prime number \nii) If the integer is a Fibonacci number \n\n2. WAP in C to compute sinx = x – x³/3! + x⁵/3! – x⁷/7! ….. Continue adding successive terms in the series until the value of the next term becomes smaller (in magnitude) than 10-5. Test the program for x = 1, x = 2, and x = 3. In each case display the number of terms used to obtain the final answer. \n\n3. WAP to generate every 3rd integer beginning with I = 2 and continue for all integers that are less than 150. Calculate the sum of those integers that are evenly divisible by 5. \n\n4. WAP to find whether a given year is a leap year or not. Modify it to generate a list of leap years between two year limits given by user. \n\n5. WAP to display the following pattern: \n                                 11 \n\n                           11  10  11 \n\n                     11   10   9   10   11 \n\n                11   10   9   8   9   10   11 \n\n6. Using Ternary / Conditional operator find the greatest among 3 numbers. \n\n7. WAP to convert a decimal number into an equivalent number of the input base. Test your program for base 2,8,10 &amp; 16. \n\n8. WAP to read a number n, and print it out digit-by-digit, as a series of words. For e.g. 123 would be printed as “one two three”. \n\n9. WAP to check whether any input +ve integer is palindrome or not. \n\n10. WAP to simulate a simple calculator (+ - / * %) that takes two operands and an operator as input and displays the result. \n\n11. WAP to find the GCD of two input +ve integer numbers. \n\n12. WAP to swap the values of two variables without using a third variable. \n\n13. Read a line of mixed text, and then write it out with all lower case and uppercase letters reversed, all digits replaced by 0s and all other characters (non-letters and nondigits) replaced by ‘*’. \n\n14. WAP to find the product of two matrices A and B. Display the source matrices and product matrix C in matrix format. \n\n15. WAP to find whether a given matrix is a triangular matrix or not. \n\n16. WAP to find the transpose of a matrix. Display the source and the transposed matrix in matrix format. \n\n17. Implement Prob. No. – 14 to 16 using functions for reading, manipulating and displaying the corresponding matrices in matrix form. \n\n18. WAP to sort a list of strings alphabetically using a 2-dim. Character array. \n\n19. WAP to display the row sum and the column – sum of an input 2- dim. Matrix. Display the source matrix with row and column sum. \n\n20. Write a recursive function to calculate S = 2 + 4 + 6 + 8 + …… +2N. Implement the function in a complete C program. \n\n21. Write a function that accepts two arguments an array and its size n. It performs Bubble up sort on the array elements. Using indirection operator ‘*’ implement this in a complete C program. Display the source and the sorted array. \n\n22. Using pointer, write a function that receives a character string and a character as argument. Delete all occurrences of this character in the string. The function should return corrected string with no holes. \n\n23. Write a function for reading character string using pointer. Calculate the length of the string (without using strlen ()). Finally print the string in reverse order, using pointer. \n\n24. Implement prob. No. 14 using pointers representation of 2 – dim. array. \n\n25. Implement prob. No. 15 using pointer representation of 2 dim. array. \n\n26. Implement prob. No. 16 using pointer representation of 2 dim. array. \n\n27. WAP to sort a list of strings into alphabetical order using array of pointers. \n\n28. Create records of 60 students, where each record has fields-name, roll, gpa and fees. Write a function update () to reduce the fees of those students who have obtained gpa greater than 8.5 by 25% of the original fees. Write a complete program to exercise this function in the main program and display all the records before and after updation. \n\n29. Define a structure that describes a hotel. It should have members that include the name, address, grade, average room charge and number of rooms. Write a function to perform the following operations: a) To print out hotels of a given grade in order of charges. b) To print out hotels with room charges less than a given value. \n\n30. WAP to concatenate the contents of two files into a third file. \n\n31. WAP to copy the content of one file into another file. Names of both the files are to be input as command line arguments"
                android:textColor="@color/textColorSecondary"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                android:textSize="20.0dip"
                android:textStyle="italic" />
        </LinearLayout>

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"

            android:gravity="center"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:text="Text Books:"
                android:textColor="@color/textColor"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                    android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1. Jery R Hanly, “Problem solving and Program design in C”, Paerson Education, 7th Edition. (T1) \n\n 2. Byron Gottfried, “Schaum's Outline of Programming with C”, McGraw-Hill. (T2) \n\n 3. E. Balaguruswamy, Programming in ANSI C, Tata McGraw-Hill. (T3) \n\n 4. R.G.Dromey, How to Solve it by Computer, Pearson Education."
                android:textColor="@color/textColorSecondary"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                android:textSize="20.0dip" />
        </LinearLayout>

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"

            android:gravity="center"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="20.0dip"
                android:text="Reference Books:"
                android:textColor="@color/textColor"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                    android:textSize="25.0dip"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10.0dip"
                android:layout_marginBottom="10.0dip"
                android:padding="5.0dip"
                android:text="1.Brian W. Kernighan and Dennis M. Ritchie, “The C Programming Language”,Prentice Hall India Learning Private Limited.(R1)"
                android:textColor="@color/textColorSecondary"
                android:textIsSelectable="true"
                android:textSize="20.0dip" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>